Finding Aid for the Louis B. Schnauber (Film Music Society) Collection PASC-M.0157
UCLA Library Special Collections
- The Grizzly-Turkey Trot, 1912; 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 173)
- Grief-Homesickness-Longing, 1924; 13 p. (Box 5, Folder 400)
- Gypsy Holiday (Box 3, Folder 260)
  Also composed by George H. Cooper and Gwynn Langdon.
- Gypsy Life (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Hacienda, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 452)
- Hail! Hail! The Gang's All Here (Box 8, Folder 752)
  Also composed by Arthur Sullivan.
- Hail, the Gang's Here (Box 9, Folder 875)
- Hail, Star of Heaven" (Ave, Maris Stella). "Saeterjentens Sondag, 1907; 17 parts (Box 13)
- Hail to America, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 436)
- Happy (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Happy Jacqueline, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 991)
- Happy Days, 1908 (Box 12, Folder 1007)
- Hark, The Herald Angels Sing (Box 9, Folder 878)
- Harlequin and Columbine, 1921; 23 p. (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Haunting Blues (Box 3, Folder 234)
  Also composed by Henry Busse.
- Havana (Box 6, Folder 525)
- Heart Throbs (Box 10, Folder 915)
- Heart Throbs, 4-4 Lento Espressivo, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 981)
- Heather Bloom, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 1003)
- Heavy Romantic (Agitato) No. 1 (Box 6, Folder 488)
- Heart of America (Box 7, Folder 655)
- Heart of Harlequin, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 1004)
- Heart's Pleading, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 997)
- Heartsease, 1906 (Box 12, Folder 996)
- Hello Little Girl, 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Henrietta (Box 3, Folder 286)
- Henry VIII, Ballet-Divertissement, 1909 (Box 12, Folder 1016)
- Herod Overture, 1920; 26 parts (Box 13)
- Herodiade. Prelude to Act IV, 1913; Massenet, Jules; Roberts, Charles J.; Carl Fischer Inc. (Box 16, Folder 1183)
- Heroical Love Drama. Prelude, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 478)
- Hesitation, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 678)
- Hey Rube, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 822)
- Hi-Yo (Box 6, Folder 560)
- The Highlanders Patrol (Box 3, Folder 285)
- A Hillside Melody, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 1009)
- Hindu (Box 8, Folder 714)
- Historical American Drama. Prelude (Box 10, Folder 903)
- Ho Hum! (Box 3, Folder 266)
- The Hobo's Reel (Box 8, Folder 728)
- The Hobbledehoy (Box 4, Folder 379)
- Hold Me (Box 9, Folder 839)
  Also composed by Ben Black
- Holy Night (Box 9, Folder 861)
- Homeland, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 1005)
- Homemade Sunshine (Box 4, Folder 349)
  Also composed by Irving Kahal and Pierre Norman.
- Honolulu Eyes (Box 5, Folder 472)
- Hope's Awakening (Box 12, Folder 1008)
- Horses (Box 9, Folder 811)
  Also composed by Richard A. Whiting
- Horsey! Keep Your Tail Up (Box 8, Folder 743)
  Also composed by Bert Kaplan.
- Hot Chocolate Rag (Box 9, Folder 850)
  Also composed by Arthur Lange
- Hula Hula, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 455)
- Hula Lou (Box 5, Folder 466)
  Also composed by Milton Charles and Wayne King
- Humoreske, 1913 (Box 12, Folder 998)
- Humoreske, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 1010)
- Hungarian Dance (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Hungarian Rag (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Hungariana March, 1917; 16 p. (Box 5, Folder 418)
  Ensemble parts ofr various instruments.
- A Hungarian Romance, 1908; 17 parts (Box 14)
- Hungarian Dance, 1912; 14 parts (Box 14)
- Hungarian Dance No.5, 1912; 14 parts (Box 14)
- Hungarian Festival March, 1913; 19 parts (Box 14)
- Hungarian Rhapsody No.4, 1921; 18 parts (Box 14)
- Hungarian Rhapsody No.6. The Carnival in Pesth, 1919; 14 parts (Box 14)
- Second Hungarian Rhapsody, 1913; 16 parts (Box 14)
- Hunkatin (Box 6, Folder 494)
- A Hunt in the Black Forest, 1894; 12 parts (Box 14)
- A Hunting Scene, 1885; 16 parts (Box 14)
- Hurry (Box 8, Folder 758)
- Hurry (Box 8, Folder 762)
- Hurdy-Gurdy Blues (Box 3, Folder 238)
- Hurry (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Hush Baby (Box 9, Folder 789)
- Hypnotic Rag (Box 1, Folder 53)
- I Found You, 1917; 10 p. (Box 2, Folder 136)
- I Get The Blues When It Rains, 1928; 32 p. (Box 2, Folder 210)
  Also composed by Harry Stoddard.
- I Kiss Your Hand, Madame, 1929; 34 p. (Box 2, Folder 208)
- I Love a Dat Man (Box 6, Folder 571)
- I Love a Little Cottage (Box 9, Folder 853)
- I Love You Best of All (Box 4, Folder 343)
- I Love You More and More (Box 6, Folder 529)
- I Loved You the First Time I Met You (Box 6, Folder 577)
- I Pagliacci: prologue, 1922; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Jungnickel, Ross; Leoncavallo, Ruggiero (Box 16, Folder 1231)
  On item: Miscellany, no. 130
  parts
- I'd Like to Tie You to My Heart Strings (Box 6, Folder 541)
- Idilio (Box 9, Folder 836)
- Idilio (Box 10, Folder 930)
- Idol of Eyes (Box 7, Folder 630)
- If Winter Comes (Summer Will Come Again) (Box 8, Folder 697)
- I'll Be Blue, Just Thinking Of You, 30 p. (Box 2, Folder 206)
- I'll Find My Way to You Wherever You Are (Box 3, Folder 269)
  Words by Grace Henry
- I'll See You Later in Slumberland (Box 4, Folder 352)
  Also composed by Frank Magine.
- I'm a Pilgrim (Box 4, Folder 362)
- I'm Alone Because I Love You (Box 3, Folder 262)
- I'm Bidding My Buddy Goodbye, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 445)
- I'm Gonna Charleston Back To Charleston (Box 3, Folder 235)
  Also composed by Lou Handman.
- I'm Gonna Get You (Box 3, Folder 252)
  Also composed by Harry Tobias and Jules Lemare.
- I'm Keepin' Company (Box 6, Folder 528)
  Also composed by Vee Lawnhurst and Dave Dreyer.
- I'm On My Way to Dublin Bay, 1915; Jerome H. Remick & Co.; Lampe, J. B. (Jens Bodewalt) (Box 15, Folder 1154)
  Patrol. On item: Humorous paraphrase on Stanley Murphy's popular song. parts.
- I'm Ridin' Straight to Heaven (On a One-Way Street) (Box 3, Folder 268)
- I'm So in Love With You (Box 3, Folder 214)
  Also composed by Irving Mills.
- I'm Thru With Love (Box 4, Folder 356)
  Also composed by Fud Livingston.
- I'm Weaving Rainbows (Box 3, Folder 240)
  Words by Bartley Costello and Ed. Rose
- I May Be Dreaming (Box 4, Folder 354)
- Immortellen Waltz (Box 8, Folder 781)
- In a Bird Store, 1916; 28 parts (Box 14)
- In A Cafe On The Road To Calais, 1931; 30 p. (Box 2, Folder 201)
  Jack LeBoir and Ray Doll also composed the work.
- In a Kingdom of Our Own (Box 4, Folder 338)
- In a Monastery Garden (Box 4, Folder 371)
- In a Pretty Little Hilly Billy Town (Box 4, Folder 358)
  Also composed by Joe Burke.
- In a Tent (Box 1, Folder 93)
  Also composed by Frank Magine and Joe Lyons.
- In an Opium Den (Box 6, Folder 549)
- In My Garden of Eden For Two (Box 6, Folder 567)
- In Old Madeira (Box 6, Folder 514)
  Also composed by Monte Carlo.
- In Rapture Sweet (Box 3, Folder 247)
- In Santa Fe (Box 6, Folder 527)
- In the Clock Store, 1893; 13 parts (Box 14)
- In the Garden of the Gods (Box 6, Folder 568)
- Incidental Miniatures. A Regal Scene (Box 6, Folder 487)
- Incidental Miniatures. Maestoso Allegro (Box 6, Folder 486)
- Indian or Battle Hurry (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Indian Butterfly (Naomi) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  Also composed by Henry Lodge and Billy Stone.
- Indian Dawn (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Indian Intermezzo No. 17 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Indian Misterioso (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Incidental Miniatures (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Indian Lament (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Indian Lament No. 18(B) (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Indian Love Song No. 18(A) (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Indian Music (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Indian Mystical (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Indian Plaintive (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Indian War Dance No. 19 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Indian War Song (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Indigo Blues (Box 3, Folder 224)
- In Old Manila, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 465)
- Fantasia on the Opera "Inquisitive Women", 1911; 15 parts (Box 14)
- Fantasia on the Opera "Inquisitive Women", 1911; 15 parts (Box 14)
- In the Army Now (Box 9, Folder 857)
  Handwritten parts
- Intense Grief, 1924; 24 p. (Box 2, Folder 153)
  Ensemble parts for various instruments. From Carl Fischer's "Film Themes."
  Chas. J. Roberts selected these extracts.
- Interlude (Alglala) (Box 11, Folder 957)
- Intensely Dramatic-Lament-Grief, 1919; 18 p. (Box 2, Folder 165)
  Work also composed by Roberts.
- Intoxication Rag, 1910; 16 p. (Box 2, Folder 176)
- Introduction and Theme No. 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Introduction and Theme No. 2 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  LUZ Feature Photo Play Edition No. 15.
- Irish Fantasia, 1896; Carl Fischer Inc.; Popp, Wilhelm (Box 15, Folder 1151)
- Irish Patrol, 1916; Cundy-Bettoney Co., Inc.; Whiting, W.K. (Box 15, Folder 1152)
  On item: no. 228.
- Italian Songs, 1912; 14 p. (Box 5, Folder 420)
- Italians in Algeria (Box 32, Folder 1)
- It's a Long Way to Berlin, But We'll Get There (Box 6, Folder 498)
- It's a Precious Little Thing Called Love, 40 p. (Box 2, Folder 212)
  Also composed by Coots.
- It's the Three Leaves of Shamrock That's Calling Me Home (Box 6, Folder 572)
- I've Got a Date at Eight (To-Night) (Box 4, Folder 347)
  Also composed by Jack Mason.
- I've Loved Only Once (Box 9, Folder 851)
  From the play "Cousin Lucy."
- Jack O'Lantern. Selection, 1918; 11 parts (Box 13)
- Jack Tar March (Box 7, Folder 668)
- Japanese Love Song (Box 6, Folder 562)
- Japaloma (Box 6, Folder 520)
- Japanese Legende (Box 32, Folder 13)
- The Japanese Sandman (Box 6, Folder 557)
- Jardin D'Amour (Box 7, Folder 652)
- Jasmo (Box 4, Folder 337)
- Jazz Band Blues (Box 7, Folder 602)
- Jealous (Box 8, Folder 741)
  Also composed by Tommie Malie and Dick Finch.
- Jeanne D'Arc (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Jericho, 1929; 37 p. (Box 2, Folder 207)
  From the F.B.O. musical screen special "Syncopation."
- Jersey Piners (Box 10, Folder 908)
- Jesus of Nazareth Passeth By (Box 4, Folder 363)
- Jewels of the Madonna (Intermezzo) (Box 11, Folder 961)
- The Jewels of the Madonna (Intermezzo II) (Box 11, Folder 963)
- The Jewels of the Madonna. Prayer, 1912; 14 parts (Box 13)
- Jollity (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Joy Rag, 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 199)
- Joy Through Tears (Box 32, Folder 17)
- The Joy Riders (Box 8, Folder 768)
- Jump Jim Crew (Box 7, Folder 600)
- June Brought The Roses, 1924; 23 p. (Box 2, Folder 137)
- June Brought the Roses, 1924; 23 p. (Box 2, Folder 137)
- Just a Baby's Prayer At Midnight (Box 9, Folder 879)
  Lyrics also composed by Joe Young.
- Just We Two, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 886)
- Just a Blue Eyed Blonde (Box 6, Folder 538)
  Also composed by Ted Fioritto.
- Just a Moment (Box 7, Folder 632)
- Just Blue (Box 3, Folder 220)
  Also composed by Victor Arden.
- Kahola-Honolulu, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 474)
- Kamenoi Ostrow Op.l0 No.22, 1909; 13 parts (Box 13)
- Kamenoi-Ostrow, 1926; 19 parts (Box 13)
- Katinka (Box 3, Folder 231)
- Keep the Home Fries Burning (Till the Boys Come Home) (Box 8, Folder 733)
- Kerry Down, 1922; Forster Music Publisher, Inc.; Roth, Edmund (Box 15, Folder 1155)
  Part of the series, Forster Melody Classics. Parts
- Kentucky Blues (Box 10, Folder 902)
- Killarney Waltzes (Box 6, Folder 569)
- The Kingdom Within Your Eyes, 1919; 18 p. (Box 2, Folder 122)
- The Kinky Kids' Parade (Box 10, Folder 911)
- The King of Love My Shepherd Is. The Holy City, 1898; 12 parts (Box 13)
- King Manfred. Romance and Prelude, op. 93 (Box 16, Folder 1230)
- Kiss Me Again, 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 127)
- Kiss Me Goodnight, 1932; 30 p. (Box 2, Folder 211)
  Also composed by Horatio Nicholls.
- Kismet (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Kiss Me Again (Box 3, Folder 243)
- Kiss Me Again (Box 4, Folder 336)
- Kiss Me Good Night (Box 6, Folder 533)
  Also composed by Joseph A. Burke.
- The Kiss Waltz (Box 3, Folder 289)
  from "Her Soldier Boy"
- K-K-K-Katy (Box 8, Folder 737)
- Knick Knocks Rag, 1915; 15 p. (Box 2, Folder 191)
- Knick Knocks Rag, 1915; 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 191)
- Ky-Isses (Kisses) (Box 32, Folder 3)
- A La Mode (Box 3, Folder 276)
- La Brasiliana (Box 10, Folder 898)
- Lady Hamilton Waltz (Box 7, Folder 643)
- Lady of the Nile (Box 1, Folder 80)
  Also composed by Isham Jones.
- Lady Play Your Mandolin (Box 3, Folder 257)
- The Lady Picking Mulberries (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Lakme. Selections, 1917; Carl Fischer Inc.; Roberts, Charles J.; Delibes, Léo; 14 parts (Box 15, Folder 1137)
- Lament-Anguish-Grief, 1924; 12 p. (Box 5, Folder 393)
- Lamentoso, 1917; 8 p. (Box 2, Folder 166)
  Berg series no. 68.
- Lamentoso, No. 46, 1917; 10 p. (Box 2, Folder 170)
  Berg series.
- Lament-Great Sorrow, 18 p. (Box 5, Folder 395)
- Lamentoso, 1919; 19 parts (Box 13)
- Lamento (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Lamento (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Lamento-Intensely Dramatic (Box 4, Folder 390)
- Lamentoso (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Landing of the Troops (Box 7, Folder 667)
- A La Paree (Box 3, Folder 274)
- L'Arlesienne Fantasia, 1913; Cundy-Bettoney Co., Inc.; Robinson, F.E.; Bizet, Georges; 11 parts (Box 15, Folder 1136)
- Ballet "La Source", Incantation, Romance, Introduction and Mazurka, Finale, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 983)
- La Sevillana, 1907 (Box 12, Folder 999)
- A Legend of Erin, 1922; Belwin, Inc.; Aborn, Morris; Johnson, Eleanor; 16 parts (Box 15, Folder 1139)
- Legende. Op.66 Celtic Dance, 1912; 17 parts (Box 13)
- Legend of the Sea (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Les Contes d'Hoffmann (Box 12, Folder 986)
- Let a Little Pleasure Interfere With Business (Box 6, Folder 539)
- Let Me Call You Sweetheart (Box 8, Folder 747)
- Let Me Hum a Hymn to Her Tonight (Box 3, Folder 256)
  Also composed by Little Jack Little.
- Let Us Dance, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 837)
  Also composed by Adolf Philipp
- Light Romantic Theme No. 2, 1917; 10 p. (Box 2, Folder 169)
  A.B.C. Photo-play edition.
- Light Cavalry-Poet and Peasant (Box 4, Folder 319)
- Light Romantic Theme No. 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  A.B.C. Feature Photo Play Edition.
- Light Romantic Theme No. 3 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  A.B.C. Feature Photo Play Edition No. 16.
- Like melting tones it rises, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 1011)
- Lila. Preghiera, 1916; 16 parts (Box 13)
- Listen to This (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A Little Story, 1911; 12 parts (Box 13)
- Little Dot (Box 4, Folder 337)
- Little Flower Garden Caprice, 1923; 17 parts (Box 13)
- Lovely Flowers, 1919; 18 p. (Box 2, Folder 164)
- Lo-La-Lo, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 454)
  Also composed by Arthur Lange.
- Lonely Hours (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Longing, 17 parts (Box 13)
- Longing For Home (Heimweh). "Loreley", 1897; 12 parts (Box 13)
- Look in the Looking Glass (Box 3, Folder 258)
- Lord God, Protect the Czar (Box 9, Folder 859)
  Inside cover is black and white film announcement.
- Lost Paradise Nocturne, 1922; 18 parts (Box 13)
- Lost Paradise (Box 32, Folder 10)
- The Lost Chord. Good Bye, 1915; 21 parts (Box 13)
- Louise, 35 p. (Box 2, Folder 209)
  Theme song of the Paramount film "Innocents Of Paris."
- A Love Song, 1910; 23 pages; Ensemble parts for various instruments (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Love is King March (Box 9, Folder 820)
- Love Me, 1919; 16 p. (Box 2, Folder 138)
- Love Song Orientale No. 59 (Box 8, Folder 721)
- Love Theme-Love Story-Serenade (Box 9, Folder 890)
  From Carl Fischer "Film Themes."
- Love-Romance-Plaintive, 19 p. (Box 5, Folder 394)
- Love-Romance-Sadness, 1924; 14 p. (Box 2, Folder 157)
- Love's Awakening (Box 9, Folder 788)
- Love's Declaration, 1923; 15 parts (Box 13)
- Love's Hesitation, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 676)
- Lovin' You, 1926; 10 p. (Box 2, Folder 141)
  Also composed by Sara Green.
- The Love Waltz, 1927; 28 p. (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Love Fancies, 1911; 12 parts (Box 13)
- Love in April, 1917; 13 parts (Box 13)
- Love in Springtime (Box 4, Folder 302)
- Love Melody-Plaintive Narrative (Box 4, Folder 384)
- Love Song. Songe d'Enfant (A Child's Dream), 1913; 13 parts (Box 13)
- Love Stars (Box 7, Folder 644)
- Love Theme (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Love's Sweet Hour, 1922; 15 parts (Box 13)
- The Love Dance, 1910; 14 parts (Box 13)
- Love Theme, 1918; 16 p. (Box 2, Folder 158)
- Loyal Comrades (Box 9, Folder 800)
- Lucia. Donizetti's Sextet (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Lucinda's Serenade (Box 11, Folder 944)
- "Ludovic" Overture, 1887; 20 parts (Box 13)
- Lu-Lu-Fado (Box 9, Folder 832)
- Lullaby (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Lulu Von Linden (Box 3, Folder 279)
  From the comic operetta, "The Eternal Waltz."
- The Lure of Crimson, 1925; 17 parts (Box 13)
- The Lure of Crimson, 1925; 17 parts (Box 13)
- Lyric Pieces, No. 1 Gade, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1012)
- Lyric Pieces, No. 2 Canon, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 1017)
- Lyric Pieces, No. 2 Elegie, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1012)
- Lyric Pieces, No. 3 Gratitude, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1012)
- Lyric Pieces, No. 3 Little Bird, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 1017)
- Lyric Pieces, No. 4 Grandmother's Minuet, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1012)
- Lyric Pieces, No. 4 Scherzo, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 1017)
- Lyric Pieces, No. 5 At the Cradle, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1012)
- Lyric Pieces, No. I Albumleaf, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 1017)
- Lyric Suite I. Shepherd's Boy, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1014)
- Lyric Suite, II. Norwegian rustic march, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1014)
- Lyric Suite, III. Notturno-Aftenstemning, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1014)
- Lyric Suite, IV. March of the Dwarfs-Troldtog, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1014)
- Madriola (Box 10, Folder 897)
  Also composed by Joseph Samuels
- Maestoso (Box 6, Folder 489)
- The Magic of Your Eyes (Box 8, Folder 709)
- Magic Sunbeams (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Manzanillo, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 895)
- Mandarin Dance (Box 6, Folder 548)
- Manolos y Manolas (Box 6, Folder 517)
- March "Surrender" (Box 9, Folder 814)
- March Themes (Box 9, Folder 862)
- Maria, My Own, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 688)
- Marimba (Box 5, Folder 468)
- March and One Step (Box 4, Folder 321)
  From The Velvet Lady.
- March Crimson (Box 4, Folder 314)
- March of the Iron Horse (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Marche Hongroise. Hungarian March, 1914; 14 parts (Box 14)
- Marche Mignonne, op. 15, no. 2, 1920; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Poldini, Eduard; Rapee, Erno (Box 16, Folder 1228)
  On item: Galaxy no. 173
- Marche Slave, 1911; 23 parts (Box 13)
- Maritana Selection Op.382, 1900; Carl Fischer Inc.; Moses-Tobani, Theo.; Wallace, W.V.; 13 parts (Box 15, Folder 1132)
- Maria My Own (Box 6, Folder 534)
- Mariette (Box 3, Folder 271)
- Maritza (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Martinique, 1906; Langey, Otto; Loraine, William; M. Witmark & Sons (Box 16, Folder 1216)
- Mascagni's Faewell, 1903; Continental Music Co.; Volger, Julius (Box 16, Folder 1213)
- The Massacre (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Maxixe Briolette (Box 6, Folder 524)
- May Dreams, 1918; Belwin, Inc.; Borch, Gaston (Box 16, Folder 1215)
- Mazurka, op. 50, no. 3, Carl Fischer Inc.; Chopin, Frédéric; Glazounow, Aleksandr Konstantinovich; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1218)
- Me-Ow (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Mecca (Box 8, Folder 774)
- Meditation, 1894; Langey, Otto; Tchaikovsky (Box 16, Folder 1214)
  On item: Galaxy, No. 186.
- Meditation, 1921; von Blon, Franz; Carl Fischer Inc.; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1211)
- Meditation, 1924; Baron, Maurice; Belwin, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 1212)
- Meditation, op. 32, 1918; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Glazounow, Aleksandr Konstantinovich; Langey, Otto (Box 16, Folder 1222)
- Melida, 1927; Carl Fischer Inc.; Elie, Justin; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1223)
- Melodie, 1916; Huerter, Charles; Kiefert, C.; Boston Music Co. (Box 16, Folder 1225)
- Melodie, 1918; Carl Fischer Inc.; Gluck; Roberts, Charles J.; Sgambati (Box 16, Folder 1217)
- Melodie, op. 3, no. 3, 1918; Carl Fischer Inc.; Rachmaninoff, Sergei; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1226)
  Score and parts
- Melodie, op. 10, no. 4, 1919; Carl Fischer Inc.; Rachmaninoff, Sergei; Roberts, Charles J. (Box 16, Folder 1227)
- Melody Rag (Box 1, Folder 67)
- The Melody of the Bell No. 12 (Box 4, Folder 368)
- Memories, 1925; Sam Fox Publishing Co.; St. Clair, Floyd J. (Box 16, Folder 1221)
  On item: Lib. No. 119
  parts.
- Memories of Childhood-Mother Song (Box 4, Folder 382)
- Memory's Garden, 1923; Denni, Lucien; J.W. Jenkins Sons Music Co. (Box 16, Folder 1224)
- Men of Valor (Box 4, Folder 337)
- Mendelssohn Melodies (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Menuet (Box 33, Folder 12)
- The Merry Maiden (Box 8, Folder 730)
- Mercedes (Box 3, Folder 300)
- Merry Go Round Waltz (Box 7, Folder 669)
- The Merry Wives of Windsor Overture, 1912; 14 parts (Box 13)
- The Merry Wives of Windsor. Overture, 1912; 19 parts (Box 13)
- Mexicana No. 20 (Box 10, Folder 900)
- Midnight Rag, 1912; 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 186)
- The Midnight Trot, 1914; 11 p. (Box 2, Folder 187)
- Mighty Lak' a rose (Box 4, Folder 337)
- Mighty Lak'a Rose (Box 7, Folder 616)
  Also composed by Frank W. McKee.
- The Mikado (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Military Life, 12 p. (Box 5, Folder 422)
- Mill, The, op. 17, Jensen, Adolf; Roberts, Charles J.; Carl Fischer Inc. (Box 16, Folder 1219)
- Mine Yesterday-His Today, 1931; 28 p. (Box 2, Folder 203)
  Also composed by Lee David.
- Minor and Major Theme (Box 1, Folder 12)
  LUZ Feature Photo Play Edition No. 3. Compiled by Ernst Luz.
- Minor Theme No. 1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Minuet (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Minuet from G Minor Symphony (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Minuet from the Eb Symphony (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Misery Rag (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Mississippi Volunteers (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mock Morris, 1914; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Grainger, Percy; Langey, Otto (Box 15, Folder 1145)
  Orch. Miscellany, no. 54.
- Moder Svea (Box 11, Folder 969)
  Also composed by Borch.
- Molly on the Shore, 1914; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Grainger, Percy; Langey, Otto (Box 15, Folder 1149)
  From the British Folk Music Settings series, no. 1. On item, "Misc., no. 128.
- Monmartre, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 448)
- Monte Cristo (Box 9, Folder 848)
  Also composed by Jean Schwartz
- Monte Carlo (Box 7, Folder 664)
- Montrose (Box 7, Folder 671)
- Moon Magic. Rose of Samarkand, 1925; 17 parts (Box 14)
- Moon Shadows Reverie, 1920; 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 116)
- The Moon Shines On the Moonshine (Box 8, Folder 749)
- The Moose (Box 9, Folder 803)
- Moon Shadows Reverie, 1920; 20 p. (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Moon Winks (Box 6, Folder 570)
- Moonlight Saving Time (Box 3, Folder 263)
  Also composed by Harry Richman
- Moonlit Garden, 1924; 21 p. (Box 2, Folder 113)
  From "Sam Fox Cinema Impressions Vol 1."
- Moonlight Memories (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Moonlight Shadows (Box 7, Folder 613)
- The More You Hurt Me (The More You Make Me Care) (Box 4, Folder 342)
- Morning (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Morning Journals (Box 4, Folder 301)
- Monstrat Viam (Box 4, Folder 325)
- Mother (A Word that Means the World to Me) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Mother in Ireland, 1923; Kahn, Griffen; Lange, Arthur; Lyman; Waterson, Berliin & Snyder Co. (Box 15, Folder 1153)
  Symphonette. Parts On item, paraphrased and scored by Arthur Lange.
- Mother Mine (Box 8, Folder 694)
  Also composed by Larry Shay.
- Mother o' Mine (Box 3, Folder 244)
- Mountain Music (Box 11, Folder 973)
- Musical Thought, 1920; Belwin, Inc.; Henneberg, Paul; Titlebaum, J. (Box 16, Folder 1210)
- My Buddy (Box 33, Folder 15)
- My Cairo Love (Box 1, Folder 96)
- My Love of Long Ago (Box 4, Folder 334)
- My Gee Gee From the Fiji Isle, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 469)
  Also composed by Lew Brown
- My Heart Will Tell Me So, 1926; 24 p. (Box 2, Folder 125)
  Blaufuss is the surname of the work's second composer.
- My Hero (Box 8, Folder 701)
- My Isle of Golden Dreams, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 456)
- My Isle of Golden Dreams (Box 5, Folder 464)
- My Little Bimbo Down on the Bamboo Isle, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 457)
  Also composed by Grant Clarke.
- My Skylark Love, 1913; 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 135)
- Mysterioso (Box 36, Folder 13)
- My Uncle Sammy Gals, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 815)
- Na-Jo (Box 1, Folder 47)
  Also composed by Walter Holliday.
- Nadja (Box 8, Folder 713)
- Narcissus, 1920; Boston Music Co.; Loud, W.E.; Nevin, Ethelbert (Box 16, Folder 1197)
- Nat Johnson's Rag, 1912; 12 p. (Box 2, Folder 180)
- National Defense, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 434)
- National Emblem (Box 9, Folder 791)
- National Melodies (Box 9, Folder 842)
- The Naval Review (Box 5, Folder 477)
  From the "Hawkes Photo Play Series"
- Neapolitan Nights (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Neath the Moon (Box 7, Folder 640)
- Needing You, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 690)
- Neutral Society Drama. Prelude (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Nevertheless, De Sylva, Brown and Henderson, Inc.: New York; 37 p. (Box 2, Folder 205)
  Harry Ruby also composed the work.
- New Mown Hay, 1902; Continental Music Co.; Matthews, Jason V.; Smith, Lee Orean (Box 16, Folder 1200)
- New York Rag (Box 1, Folder 70)
- A Night on the Prado, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 891)
- A Night Scene (Box 36, Folder 13)